This is really the last time.
Whatever we draw,
we do, okay?
Are you ready?
Ready.
Then let's...
I'm in charge of cleaning.
I'll set up the venue.
I'll go shopping.
Okay, since there are no objections,
let's get ready.
I have one.
What are you doing?
Giving money to this profiteer for purchases
is no different from throwing a rat into a rice bin.
Why am I the rat?
Like this,
is it okay?
No.
If she goes out to buy things,
she will only buy nearly expired food
and poor quality stationery.
I'm just frugal.
I look for value,
not taking petty advantages.
You look for value?
How about this?
I'll be in charge of buying things,
and you guys clean up and set up the venue.
Is that okay?
Sure.
I'll sweep the floor, and you clean the AC.
Why can't I sweep the floor and you clean the AC?
You're tall, so you clean the AC.
I have to clean the AC just because I'm tall?
Then ask Yao Ming to clean it for you.
I'll even call him for you.
Hello, Mr. Yao?
Can you help her clean the AC?
Mr. Yao isn't here.
But Mr. Tang is.
How about this?
I'll be in charge of cleaning and decorating the place.
You guys are in charge of grocery shopping.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Make it quick.
Okay?
Okay.
I think this smell
doesn't quite match my recent vibe.
What vibe?
The vibe of an unscrupulous merchant?
You.
What's wrong with me saying I don't like it?
I don't care if you like it or not.
Please hurry up and choose your items,
and go to the checkout counter to pay as soon as possible.
How about this?
You give me ten yuan,
and I'll let this go.
Then why don't you say
you'll make up the difference of 4.92 yuan?
You're arguing with me over 4.92?
Some profiteers scheme for three dollars,
even over a piece of paper.
You...
If you keep bringing up these old scores every time,
when will it ever end?
Until the end of time.
You...
Li Xinyue!
Is anybody here?
I won't forgive you.
Listen.
Listen to what?
What's that sound?
It sounds like it's coming
from the shelves.
You...
Don't talk nonsense.
Be quiet.
It's coming this way.
Stop talking. Stop talking. Stop talking.
Just kidding.
You were kidding?
So you're afraid of the dark.
I guess you must not have many friends.
What's wrong with having no friends?
As long as I eat well, drink well, and feel good,
that's enough.
You're really carefree.
How can you still fall asleep?
I didn't expect
you to be this cute when you're asleep.
How can an apology be enough?
Shouldn't there be some compensation for mental distress or something?
The supermarket has fulfilled its obligation to inform.
Inform?
Did you hear it?
Just stop talking.
If you hadn't been fighting with that cleaner,
would this have happened?
Zhang Yang is afraid of the dark.
I'd say just a little.
Slightly.
You could say it's just a scratch on the surface.
We haven't even opened yet,
and we already have a customer coming?
It should be the business license.
Hello.
I'm here to apply for the receptionist position.
Receptionist?
You came just in time.
Xinyue.
Your package needs to be signed by yourself.
Hurry up, Xinyue.
Coming.
What's wrong? Can't you eat without me?
Of course. We had to wait for you.
You make it sound like we're really close.
I think we are.
All right.
Today, we are here to welcome Tang Yi and Yiyi.
As the saying goes,
with a full stomach and warm clothes, nothing is hard.
Today we will eat and drink to our hearts' content,
and everything will go smoothly in the future.
Wishing Chenggong Travel Agency a grand opening
and may we make a fortune every day.
Our slogan is,
Come to Nan'an, and you will succeed.
How silly.
Friends are supposed to do silly things together.
Who's your friend?
She's been like this since childhood.
Always saying one thing and meaning another.
I think so too.
The louder the slogan, the more successful we'll be.
Our slogan is...
Louder.
The louder, the more successful.
Come to Nan'an.
We will succeed.
Cheers.
Have a taste.
Oolong tea.
They say it's one of the top three famous teas in the province.
Not in the mood.
Such good stuff.
Good tea.
Take it easy.
The first step is always the hardest.
The beginning is the hardest part.
At least give me a start.
Can't this wind chime ring when someone comes?
Don't hang it up.
It rings whenever the wind blows.
I always think someone has come.
Let's go for a walk.
Not in the mood.
Don't you think going for a walk
might help?
You mean
taking a walk will bring inspiration, right?
I didn't mean that.
I meant
taking a walk might make you feel better.
A good composition
will make more people want to appreciate it.
Just like a good restaurant
will attract more customers.
Advantages and reputation,
that's exactly what we lack.
You learn pretty fast.
You're just too slow.
This is called the golden spiral composition.
Don't mention the golden spiral in front of me.
Why?
I hold a grudge against the golden spiral.
We are irreconcilable,
and at odds with each other.
If I find out who he is,
I will definitely seek revenge
and give him a taste of his own medicine.
The golden spiral you mentioned,
is it a person?
Of course not.
He's a weirdo.
I used to work at an online store selling photo paper.
I accidentally sent him the wrong photo paper.
He wrote me a 2,000-word negative review.
Complain about me,
causing all kinds of trouble.
Extortion.
Consumer rights protection has become extortion.
I will complain about you,
I'll write a 2,000-word essay to complain about you.
I was working fine.
My supervisor didn't like me in the first place.
Now look,
he just fired me.
I have no job.
You wouldn't hate me this much for such a little thing, would you?
Of course I would.
I'm just that petty,
I just hold a grudge.
Then hate him to death.
Why are you so worked up?
Why would I be worked up?
I...
I'm just empathizing.
Zhang Yang.
Didn't you say before
that you stayed here because you like Nan'an?
You don't have to keep working as a receptionist at my sister's shop.
Doing this, photography, travel shoots,
doesn't it make much more money?
It's a part-time job.
And the two don't conflict.
They don't conflict?
No.
They don't conflict.
If they don't conflict,
why are you stuttering
and avoiding my eyes?
Feeling guilty?
Damn it.
Did she find out?
Stay calm. Don't panic.
Don't you know men and women shouldn't be too close?
Miss Li.
Getting so close to me,
could it be
that you covet my beauty?
Beauties.
Where are the beauties?
Where are they?
Instead of daydreaming,
you should think about
how to get more customers for the travel agency.
That scared me.
If she finds out I'm Golden Spiral,
I'm dead meat.
Wait for me.
I'd be waiting until dark.
Here are your Honglai chicken feet.
Eat them while they're hot. They won't taste as good cold.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, thank you.
Can I take a picture with you?
Well-proportioned muscles,
a friendly smile,
and reasonable prices.
This is a good marketing strategy.
Is he selling chicken feet or muscles?
The food industry is so competitive now.
It's called visual marketing.
Our travel agency can do the same.
We can find a good-looking guide.
Do I not look good?
Alright, alright.
You are the
refreshing type.
You're different.
I work out too.
It's just that my muscles
are more reserved.
Let's go.
Places that use muscles to attract customers
definitely don't have good food.
If you're not eating, I will.
Marketing can't...
Boss, I want a super large portion of chicken feet.
Okay.
You two are tourists, right?
Honglai chicken feet are a specialty of our Nan'an.
They taste very good.
I know.
Um, boss, I want to ask you something.
Are there more tourists
or locals among your usual customers?
Boss, can you hurry up?
We are in a hurry.
Okay.
It will be ready soon.
Your Honglai chicken feet are ready.
Welcome to come again.
Thank you.
We will come often.
I just wanted to ask you, um...
Not necessarily.
We are very busy.
Let's go.
Don't push, line up.
Everyone will get some.
I want some too.
Let's go.
What are you doing? What's the rush?
I was just about to discuss with someone
to see if we should collaborate on some
food tours or something.
Who asked you to keep staring at him?
What?
I mean,
the most important things for our travel agency are services and routes.
Don't do that muscle marketing stuff.
Well,
even if I wanted to, I don't have any.
You, just eat your chicken feet.
Delicious.
Try it.
I won't eat it.
It's really good.